<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.okteta.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxOktetaxx</name>
  <summary>Hex editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Editor hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Hexa editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Hex-Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Hexbewerker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Editor hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Editor hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Redactor hexazecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Hex editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Hexeditor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Шістнадцятковий редактор</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxHex editorxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Okteta is a simple editor for the raw data of files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Okteta és un editor senzill per les dades de fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Okteta ist ein einfacher Editor für die Rohdaten von Dateien.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Okteta is een eenvoudige bewerker voor de ruwe gegevens van bestanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Okteta é um editor simples para os dados em bruto dos ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Okteta é um editor simples para os dados brutos dos arquivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Okteta je jednoduchý editor na čisté údaje súborov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Okteta är en enkel editor för rådata i filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Okteta — простий редактор для безпосереднього редагування даних файлів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxOkteta is a simple editor for the raw data of files.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Caracteristici:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Values and characters shown either in two columns (the traditional display in hex editors) or in rows with the value on top of the character</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Els valors i el caràcters es mostren en dues columnes (la vista tradicional en els editors hexadecimals) o en files amb el valor a sobre del caràcter</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Werte und Zeichen können in zwei Spalten (die traditionelle Anzeige von Hexeditoren) oder in Reihen mit der Anzeige der Werte über den Zeichen dargestellt werden</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Waarden en tekens worden getoond ofwel in twee kolommen (de traditionele weergave in hex-editors) of in rijen met de waarde boven het teken.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Valores e respectivos caracteres apresentados em duas colunas (a aparência tradicional dos editores hexadecimais) ou em linhas com o valor no topo dos caracteres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Valores e respectivos caracteres apresentados em duas colunas (a aparência tradicional dos editores hexadecimais) ou em linhas com o valor no topo dos caracteres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Hodnoty a znaky zobrazené buď vo dvoch stĺpcoch (tradičné zobrazenie v hex editoroch) alebo v riadkoch s hodnotou nad znakom</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Värden och tecken visas antingen i två kolumner (det traditionella sättet i hexadecimala editorer) eller i rader med värdet ovanför tecknet </li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Значення та символи може бути показано або у два стовпчики (типовий формат перегляду у шістнадцяткових редакторах) або у форматі рядків, де значення буде показано над символом.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxValues and characters shown either in two columns (the traditional display in hex editors) or in rows with the value on top of the characterxx</li>
      <li>Editing and navigating similar to a text editor</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Edició i navegació semblant a un editor de text</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Bearbeiten und navigieren ähnlich wie in einem Texteditor</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bewerken en navigeren is gelijk aan die in een tekstbewerker</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Edição e navegação semelhantes a um editor de texto</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Edição e navegação semelhantes a um editor de texto</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Úprava a navigácia podobná ako v textovom editore</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Redigering och navigering liknar en texteditor</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Панелі редагування і навігації, подібні на відповідні панелі текстового редактора.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEditing and navigating similar to a text editorxx</li>
      <li>Customizable data views, with loadable and storable profiles</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vistes de dades que es poden personalitzar, amb perfils que es poden carregar i emmagatzemar</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Aan te passen weergave met profielen die zijn te laden en op te slaan</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Vistas de dados personalizadas, com perfis que podem ser carregados e gravados</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Modos de exibição de dados personalizados, com perfis que podem ser gravados e carregados</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Prispôsobiteľné pohľady údajov s načítateľnými a uložiteľnými profilmi</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Anpassningsbar datavisning, med profiler som kan läsas in och sparas</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Придатні до налаштовування панелі перегляду даних з можливістю завантаження та збереження профілів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCustomizable data views, with loadable and storable profilesxx</li>
      <li>Tools dockable on all sides or floating</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Eines acoblables en totes les vores o flotants</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Hulpmiddelen die aan alle kanten zijn te verankeren of zweven</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ferramentas acopláveis a todos os lados ou flutuantes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramentas acopláveis em todos os lados ou flutuantes</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nástroje uchytiteľné na všetkých stranách alebo plávajúce</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Verktyg kan dockas på alla sidor eller vara fristående</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість довільного розташування або повного від’єднання від вікна панелей інструментів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTools dockable on all sides or floatingxx</li>
      <li>Numerical encodings: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binary</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Codificacions numèriques: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binari</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Zahlenkodierung: Hexadezimal, Dezimal, Oktal und Binär</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Numerieke coderingen: hexadecimaal, decimaal, octaal, binair</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Codificações numéricas: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binário</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Codificações numéricas: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal e Binário</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Numerické kódovania: hexadecimálne, decimálne, osmičkové a binárne</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Numeriska kodningar: Hexadecimal, decimal, oktal, binär</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Числові кодування: шістнадцяткове, десяткове, вісімкове, двійкове.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxNumerical encodings: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binaryxx</li>
      <li>Character encodings: All 8-bit encodings as supplied by Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Codificacions de caràcters: Totes les codificacions de 8 bits proporcionades per les Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Tekencoderingen: alle 8-bits coderingen zoals geleverd door Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Codificações de caracteres: Todas as codificações de 8 bits suportadas pelo Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Codificações de caracteres: Todas as codificações de 8 bits suportadas pelo Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Kódovania znakov: všetky 8-bitové kódovania v Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Teckenkodningar: Alla 8-bitars kodningar som tillhandahålls av Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Кодування символів: підтримка усіх 8-бітових кодувань, які підтримуються у Qt, EBCDIC.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCharacter encodings: All 8-bit encodings as supplied by Qt, EBCDICxx</li>
      <li>Fast data rendering on screen</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Renderització ràpida de dades en la pantalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Schnelles Rendern der Daten auf dem Bildschirm</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Snelle weergave van gegevens op het scherm</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Apresentação rápida dos dados no ecrã</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Apresentação rápida dos dados na tela</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Rýchle zobrazovanie údajov na obrazovke</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Snabb dataåtergivning på skärmen</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Швидкий показ даних на екрані.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFast data rendering on screenxx</li>
      <li>Multiple open files</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Múltiples fitxers oberts</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Otevření více souborů</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Mehrere geöffnete Dateien</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Meerdere geopende bestanden</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Diversos ficheiros abertos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Diversos arquivos abertos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Otváranie viacerých súborov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flera öppna filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість одночасної роботи з декількома файлами.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxMultiple open filesxx</li>
      <li>Undo/redo support</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació de desfer/refer</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Zurücknehmen und Wiederherstellen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning ongedaan maken/opnieuw</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para desfazer/refazer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para desfazer/refazer</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora Späť/Znova</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för ångra och gör om</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка скасовування та повторення дій.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxUndo/redo supportxx</li>
      <li>Structures tool for analyzing and editing based on user-creatable structure definitions</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Eina d'estructures per analitzar i editar basada en definicions d'estructures que pot crear l'usuari</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Strukturen-Werkzeug für die Untersuchung und Bearbeitung auf der Basis von benutzerdefinierten Strukturdefinitionen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Het hulpmiddel Structuren voor analyseren en bewerking op door de gebruiker gemaakte structuurdefinities</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ferramenta de estruturas para analisar e editar com base em definições de estruturas criadas pelo utilizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramenta de estruturas para análise e edição com base em definições de estruturas criadas pelo usuário</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nástroj štruktúr na analýzu a úpravu založený na používateľom vytvoriteľných definíciách štruktúr</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Strukturverktyg för att undersökning och redigering baserat på användarskapade strukturdefinitioner</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">За допомогою інструменту «Структури» можна аналізувати та редагувати масиви байтів на основі створених користувачем визначень структур.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxStructures tool for analyzing and editing based on user-creatable structure definitionsxx</li>
      <li>And more...</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">I més...</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">A další...</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Und noch mehr ...</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">En meer...</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">E mais...</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">E mais...</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Și altele...</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">A viac...</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Med mera ...</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Та багато чого іншого…</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAnd more...xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://userbase.kde.org/Okteta/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=okteta</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdesdk/okteta/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/okteta.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <updatecontact>kossebau@kde.org</updatecontact>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>okteta</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
