<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.okteta.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0 OR GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Октета</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Октета</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxOktetaxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Okteta</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Okteta</name>
  <summary>Hex editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Heksadekadni editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Editor hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Editor hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Hexa editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Hex-Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Επεξεργαστής δεκαεξαδικών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Hex editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Editor hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Binaarfailide redaktor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Editore hamaseitarra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Heksaeditori</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Éditeur hexadécimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Editor de bytes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Hexaszerkesztő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Editor (Redactor) Hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Editor Hex</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Editor esadecimale</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">16진수 편집기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Hexbewerker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Heksadesimal-redigering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytor szesnastkowy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Editor hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Editor hexadecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Redactor hexazecimal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Шестнадцатеричный редактор</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Hex editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Šestnajstiški urejevalnik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Хексадекадни уређивач</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Heksadekadni uređivač</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Хексадекадни уређивач</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Heksadekadni uređivač</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Hexeditor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Hex düzenleyici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Шістнадцятковий редактор</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxHex editorxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">十六进制编辑器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">十六進位資料編輯器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Okteta is a simple editor for the raw data of files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Okteta és un editor senzill per a les dades sense processar dels fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'Okteta és un editor senzill per a les dades sense processar dels fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Okteta ist ein einfacher Editor für die Rohdaten von Dateien.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Okteta είναι ένας απλός επεξεργαστής για τα ακατέργαστα δεδομένα αρχείων.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Okteta is a simple editor for the raw data of files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Okteta es un sencillo editor de archivos de datos en bruto.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Okteta on lihtne failide toorandmete redaktor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Okteta fitxategietako datu gordinak editatzeko editore erraz bat da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Okteta on yksinkertainen editori tiedostojen raakadatalle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Okteta est un simple éditeur pour les données brutes des fichiers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Okteta é un editor sinxelo para os datos en bruto de ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az Oktate egy egyszerű program fájlok nyers adatainak szerkesztéséhez.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Okteta es un simple editor per le datos drude de files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Okteta adalah editor sederhana untuk file-file data mentah (raw)</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Okteta è un semplice editor dei dati grezzi di un file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Okteta는 파일의 원시 데이터에 대한 간단한 편집기입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Okteta is een eenvoudige bewerker voor de ruwe gegevens van bestanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Okteta er eit veldig enkelt redigeringsprogram for rådata i filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Okteta to prosty edytor do przeglądania nieprzetworzonych danych plików.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Okteta é um editor simples para os dados em bruto dos ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Okteta é um editor simples para os dados brutos dos arquivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Okteta — простой редактор двоичных файлов</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Okteta je jednoduchý editor na čisté údaje súborov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Okteta je enostaven urejevalnik za surove podatke datotek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Октета је једноставан уређивач за сирове податке у фајловима.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Okteta je jednostavan uređivač za sirove podatke u fajlovima.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Октета је једноставан уређивач за сирове податке у фајловима.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Okteta je jednostavan uređivač za sirove podatke u fajlovima.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Okteta är en enkel editor för rådata i filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Okteta ham veri dosyaları için basit bir düzenleyicidir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Okteta — простий редактор для безпосереднього редагування даних файлів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxOkteta is a simple editor for the raw data of files.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Okteta 是款简单的文件原始数据编辑器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Okteta 是一套編輯檔案原始資料的簡易編輯器。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Svojstva:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Funksjonar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Caracteristici:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikleri:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Values and characters shown either in two columns (the traditional display in hex editors) or in rows with the value on top of the character</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Els valors i els caràcters es mostren en dues columnes (la vista tradicional en els editors hexadecimals) o en files amb el valor a sobre del caràcter</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Els valors i els caràcters es mostren en dues columnes (la vista tradicional en els editors hexadecimals) o en files amb el valor damunt del caràcter</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Werte und Zeichen können in zwei Spalten (die traditionelle Anzeige von Hexeditoren) oder in Reihen mit der Anzeige der Werte über den Zeichen dargestellt werden</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Οιτιμές και οι χαρακτήρες εμφανίζονταιή σε δύο στήλες (η παραδοσιακή παρουσίαση στους επεξεργαστές δεκαεξαδικών) ή σε γραμμέςμε την τιμή στην κορυφή του χαρακτήρα</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Values and characters shown either in two columns (the traditional display in hex editors) or in rows with the value on top of the character</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Muestra valores y caracteres en dos columnas (la vista tradicional para editores hexadecimales) o en filas con los valores encima de los caracteres</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Väärtusi ja märke võib lasta näidata kahes veerus (niisuguste redaktorite tavapärane kuvamisviis) või ridades, kus väärtus on märgi peal</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Balioak eta karaktereak bi zutabetan (editore hamaseitarretan ohiko ikuspegia) edo errenkadatan balioa karaktere gainean duela</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Arvot ja merkit näytetään joko kahdessa sarakkeessa (niin kuin perinteisesti heksaeditoreissa) tai riveittäin arvo merkin yläpuolella</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les valeurs et les caractères sont affichés soit en deux colonnes (affichage traditionnel des éditeurs hexadécimaux) soit en rangées avec la valeur au-dessus du caractère</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Os valores e caracteres poden mostrarse tanto en dúas columnas (a vista tradicional de editores de bytes) como en filas cos valores sobre os caracteres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Értékek és karakterek megjelenítése hagyományos (kétoszlopos) módon, vagy sorokban (az értékek a karakterek fölött helyezkednek el)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Valores e characteres monstrate o in duo columnas (le monstrator traditional in redactores hexadecimal) o in rangos con le valor al culmine del character</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Nilai dan karakter ditampilkan antara dua kolom (displai tradisional dalam editor hex) atau dalam row dengan nilai di atas karakter</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">I valori e i caratteri visualizzati in due colonne (la visualizzazione normale degli editor esadecimali) o in righe con il valore sopra il carattere</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">열 두 개(16진수 편집기의 기존 디스플레이) 또는 문자의 맨 위에 값이 있는 행에 표시되는 값 및 문자</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Waarden en tekens worden getoond ofwel in twee kolommen (de traditionele weergave in hex-editors) of in rijen met de waarde boven het teken.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Verdiar og teikn kan visast i to kolonnar (kjend frå klassiske heks-redigeringsprogram) eller i rader, med verdiane viste over teikna</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wartości i znaki są pokazywane albo w dwóch kolumnach (tradycyjne wyświetlanie w edytorach szesnastkowych) lub w wierszach z wartością nad znakiem</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Valores e respectivos caracteres apresentados em duas colunas (a aparência tradicional dos editores hexadecimais) ou em linhas com o valor no topo dos caracteres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Valores e respectivos caracteres apresentados em duas colunas (a aparência tradicional dos editores hexadecimais) ou em linhas com o valor no topo dos caracteres</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Расположение значений и символов либо в двух столбцах (как в большинстве шестнадцатеричных редакторов), либо в строках со значениями над символами</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Hodnoty a znaky zobrazené buď vo dvoch stĺpcoch (tradičné zobrazenie v hex editoroch) alebo v riadkoch s hodnotou nad znakom</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Vrednosti in znaki, prikazani v enem od obeh stolpcev (v tradicionalnem prikazu v šestnajstiških urejevalnikih) ali v vrsticah z vrednostjo nad znakom</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Приказ вредности и знакова или у две колоне (традиционално за хексадекадне уређиваче) или по врстама са вредношћу над знаком.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Prikaz vrednosti i znakova ili u dve kolone (tradicionalno za heksadekadne uređivače) ili po vrstama sa vrednošću nad znakom.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Приказ вредности и знакова или у две колоне (традиционално за хексадекадне уређиваче) или по врстама са вредношћу над знаком.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Prikaz vrednosti i znakova ili u dve kolone (tradicionalno za heksadekadne uređivače) ili po vrstama sa vrednošću nad znakom.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Värden och tecken visas antingen i två kolumner (det traditionella sättet i hexadecimala editorer) eller i rader med värdet ovanför tecknet </li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Değerler ve karakterler ya iki sütunda (hex düzenleyicilerin geleneksel görünümü) ya da değer karakterin üzerinde olacak şekilde iki satırda görüntülenir</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Значення та символи може бути показано або у два стовпчики (типовий формат перегляду у шістнадцяткових редакторах) або у форматі рядків, де значення буде показано над символом.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxValues and characters shown either in two columns (the traditional display in hex editors) or in rows with the value on top of the characterxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">双列展示数据值和字符(传统十六进制编辑器视图)或单行字符上方显示数据</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">數值與字元可以用兩個欄位（傳統十六進制資料編輯的方式）顯示，或是在一列中將數值顯示在字元上方。</li>
      <li>Editing and navigating similar to a text editor</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Edició i navegació semblant a un editor de text</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Edició i navegació semblant a un editor de text</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Bearbeiten und navigieren ähnlich wie in einem Texteditor</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Επεξεργασία και πλοήγηση παρόμοια με επεξεργαστή κειμένου</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Editing and navigating similar to a text editor</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Edición y navegación similar a la de los editores de texto</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Redigeerimine ja liikumine nagu tavalises tekstiredaktoris</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Testu-editore baten antzeko editatzea eta nabigatzea</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Muokkaus ja siirtyminen kuin tekstieditorissa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Édition et navigation similaires à un éditeur de texte</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite editar e examinar de maneira similar a un editor de texto simple.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Szerkesztés és navigálás egy szövegszerkesztőhöz hasonlóan</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Editar e navigar de modo simile a un editor de texto</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pengeditan dan penavigasian mirip dengan editor teks</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Modifica e navigazione simili ad un editor di testo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">텍스트 편집기와 유사한 편집 및 탐색</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bewerken en navigeren is gelijk aan die in een tekstbewerker</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Redigering og navigering som eit vanleg skriveprogram</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Edytowanie i poruszanie się po programie podobnie jak w edytorach tekstowych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Edição e navegação semelhantes a um editor de texto</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Edição e navegação semelhantes a um editor de texto</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Редактирование и навигация приближена к интерфейсу текстового редактора</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Úprava a navigácia podobná ako v textovom editore</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Urejanje in krmarjenje, podobno tistemu v urejevalniku besedil</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Уређивање и кретање слично уређивачу текста.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Uređivanje i kretanje slično uređivaču teksta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Уређивање и кретање слично уређивачу текста.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Uređivanje i kretanje slično uređivaču teksta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Redigering och navigering liknar en texteditor</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Metin düzenleyicilere benzer düzenleme ve gezinme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Панелі редагування і навігації, подібні на відповідні панелі текстового редактора.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEditing and navigating similar to a text editorxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">类似于文本编辑器的编辑和导航</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">編輯與導覽類似一般文字編輯器</li>
      <li>Customizable data views, with loadable and storable profiles</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vistes de dades que es poden personalitzar, amb perfils que es poden carregar i emmagatzemar</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vistes de dades que es poden personalitzar, amb perfils que es poden carregar i emmagatzemar</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Benutzerdefinierte Datenansichten mit Profilen, die gespeichert und geladen werden können.</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Προσαρμόσιμες προβολές δεδομένων με φορτώσιμα και αποθηκεύσιμα προφίλ</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Customisable data views, with loadable and storable profiles</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vistas personalizadas de datos, con perfiles que se pueden guardar y cargar</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kohandatavad andmevaated laaditavate ja salvestatavate profiilidega</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Datuen ikuspegi moldagarriak, profilak zamatu eta gorde daitezke</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Muokattavissa olevat datanäkymät; ladattavat ja tallennettavat profiilit</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Vues de données personnalisables ; il est possible de charger et d'enregistrer des profils</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">As vistas de datos poden personalizarse, e poden cargarse e almacenarse perfís.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Testre szabható adatnézetek, betölthető és menthető profilokkal</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Vistas de datos personalisabile, con profilos cargabile e immagazinabile</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tampilan data yang dapat dikustomisasi, dapat dimuat, dan profil yang dapat disimpan</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Viste dei dati configurabili, con profili caricabili e salvabili</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">불러오기 및 저장이 가능한 프로필을 사용하여 사용자 정의 가능한 데이터 보기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Aan te passen weergave met profielen die zijn te laden en op te slaan</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Kan skreddarsy datavisingar og lagra dei som eigne profilar</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Własne widoki danych wraz z możliwością wczytywania i zachowywania profili</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Vistas de dados personalizadas, com perfis que podem ser carregados e gravados</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Modos de exibição de dados personalizados, com perfis que podem ser gravados e carregados</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Настраиваемые панели просмотра данных с возможностью сохранения и загрузки профилей</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Prispôsobiteľné pohľady údajov s načítateľnými a uložiteľnými profilmi</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Prilagodljivi pogledi podatkov, s profili za nalaganje in shranjevanje</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Прилагодљиви прикази података, уписивање и учитавање профила.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Prilagodljivi prikazi podataka, upisivanje i učitavanje profila.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Прилагодљиви прикази података, уписивање и учитавање профила.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Prilagodljivi prikazi podataka, upisivanje i učitavanje profila.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Anpassningsbar datavisning, med profiler som kan läsas in och sparas</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yüklenebilir ve saklanabilir profillerle özelleştirilebilir veri görünümleri</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Придатні до налаштовування панелі перегляду даних з можливістю завантаження та збереження профілів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCustomizable data views, with loadable and storable profilesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">可自定义数据视图，装入和保存视图配置</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">客製化的資料檢視，可載入並儲存設定檔</li>
      <li>Tools dockable on all sides or floating</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Eines acoblables en totes les vores o flotants</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Eines acoblables en totes les vores o flotants</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Werkzeuge können an allen Seiten verankert oder freischwebend benutzt werden</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εργαλεία έτοιμα για διαχειριστές εργασιών σε όλες τις πλευρές ή αιωρούμενα</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Tools dockable on all sides or floating</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Cajas de herramientas empotrables o flotantes</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Tööriistad, mida saab dokkida igale küljele või muuta hõljuvaks</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Tresna flotagarriak edo alde guztietan aingura daitezkeenak</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Työkalut, jotka voi telakoida mihin tahansa laitaan tai antaa kellua vapaasti</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les outils peuvent être disposés de chaque côté ou flottants</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">As ferramentas poden acoplarse por toda a interface ou quedar flotando sobre ela.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Bármely oldalon dokkolható vagy lebegő eszköztárak</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Instrumentos stivabile sur omne lateres o fluctuante</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Peralatan yang dapat di-dock pada semua sisi atau mengambang</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Strumenti agganciabili su qualsiasi lato o liberi</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">모든 측면 또는 플로팅 시 도킹 가능</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Hulpmiddelen die aan alle kanten zijn te verankeren of zweven</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Verktøya kan dokkast på alle sidene, eller flyta fritt</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Narzędzia pływające lub z możliwością dokowania na wszystkich stronach</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ferramentas acopláveis a todos os lados ou flutuantes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramentas acopláveis em todos os lados ou flutuantes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Перемещаемые панели</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nástroje uchytiteľné na všetkých stranách alebo plávajúce</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Orodja, ki jih je mogoče sidrati na vse strani ali pustiti plavajoča</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Алатке усидриве уз било коју страну, или плутајуће.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Alatke usidrive uz bilo koju stranu, ili plutajuće.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Алатке усидриве уз било коју страну, или плутајуће.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Alatke usidrive uz bilo koju stranu, ili plutajuće.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Verktyg kan dockas på alla sidor eller vara fristående</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kenarlara tutturulmuş veya kayan araçlar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість довільного розташування або повного від’єднання від вікна панелей інструментів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTools dockable on all sides or floatingxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">四周可停靠工具面板也可浮动</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">工具可以嵌在每一個側邊，或是浮出來</li>
      <li>Numerical encodings: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binary</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Codificacions numèriques: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binari</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Codificacions numèriques: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binari</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Zahlenkodierung: Hexadezimal, Dezimal, Oktal und Binär</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αριθμητικές κωδικοποιήσεις: Δεκαεξαδική, δεκαδική, οκταδική, δυαδική</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Numerical encodings: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binary</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Codificaciones numéricas (hexadecimal, decimal, octal, binaria)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Arvukodeeringud: kuueteistkümnend-, kümnend-, kaheksand- ja kahendsüsteemis</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Zenbaki kodeketa: hamaseitarra, hamartarra, zortzitarra, bitarra</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Lukujen koodaukset: heksa, desimaali, oktaali, binaari</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Codage des valeurs : hexadécimal, décimal, octal, binaire</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Pode mostrar os valores numéricos en notacións hexadecimal, decimal, octal e binaria.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Numerikus kódolások: hexadecimális, decimális, oktális, bináris</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Codificationes Numeric: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binari</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pengenkodean nomerik: Heksadesimal, Desimal, Oktal, Biner</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Codifiche numeriche: esadecimale, decimale, ottale e binaria</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">숫자 인코딩: 16진수, 10진수, 8진수, 2진수</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Numerieke coderingen: hexadecimaal, decimaal, octaal, binair</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Numeriske kodingar: heksadesimal, desimal, oktal, binær</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kodowania numeryczne: szesnastkowe, dziesiętne, ósemkowe, dwójkowe</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Codificações numéricas: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binário</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Codificações numéricas: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal e Binário</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка шестнадцатеричной, десятичной, восьмеричной и двоичной записи чисел</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Numerické kódovania: hexadecimálne, decimálne, osmičkové a binárne</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Številska kodiranja: šestnajstiško, desetiško, osmiško, dvojiško</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Бројевна кодирања: хексадекадно, декадно, октално, бинарно.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Brojevna kodiranja: heksadekadno, dekadno, oktalno, binarno.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Бројевна кодирања: хексадекадно, декадно, октално, бинарно.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Brojevna kodiranja: heksadekadno, dekadno, oktalno, binarno.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Numeriska kodningar: Hexadecimal, decimal, oktal, binär</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Sayısal kodlama: On altılık, Onluk, Sekizlik, İkilik</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Числові кодування: шістнадцяткове, десяткове, вісімкове, двійкове.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxNumerical encodings: Hexadecimal, Decimal, Octal, Binaryxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">数字编码：十六进制，十进制，八进制，二进制</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">數值編碼：十六進制，十進制，八進制或二進制</li>
      <li>Character encodings: All 8-bit encodings as supplied by Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Codificacions de caràcters: Totes les codificacions de 8 bits proporcionades per les Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Codificacions de caràcters: Totes les codificacions de 8 bits proporcionades per les Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Zeichenkodierungen: Alle Kodierungen, die von Qt und EBCDIC unterstützt werden</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Κωδικοποίηση χαρακτήρων: όλες οι 8-bit κωδικοποιήσεις όπως έρχονται από Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Character encodings: All 8-bit encodings as supplied by Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Codificaciones de caracteres (todas las codificaciones de 8 bits que proporciona Qt, EBCDIC)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Märgikodeeringud: kõik 8-bitised kodeeringud, mida toetab Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Karaktere kodeketa: Qt bidez hornitutako 8-biteko kodeketa guztiak, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Merkkikoodaukset: Kaikki Qt:n tarjoamat 8-bittiset koodaukset sekä EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Codage des caractères : tout les codages 8 bits fournis par Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Pode mostrar os caracteres en todas as codificacións baseadas en 8 bits que fornece Qt, así como en EBCDIC.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Karakterkódolások: minden, a Qt és EBCDIC által biztosított 8 bites kódolás</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Codificationes de character: Omne codificationes de 8bits como fornite per Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pengenkodean karakter: Semua pengenkodean 8-bit sebagai asupan oleh Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Codifiche dei caratteri: tutte le codifiche a 8 bit fornite da Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">문자 인코딩: Qt, EBCDIC에서 제공하는 모든 8비트 인코딩</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Tekencoderingen: alle 8-bits coderingen zoals geleverd door Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Teiknkodingar: Alle 8-bits teiknkodingar tilgjengeleg i Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kodowania znakowe: wszystkie 8-bitowe kodowania dostarczone przez Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Codificações de caracteres: Todas as codificações de 8 bits suportadas pelo Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Codificações de caracteres: Todas as codificações de 8 bits suportadas pelo Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддерживаются все 8-битные кодировки символов, имеющиеся в Qt, а также EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Kódovania znakov: všetky 8-bitové kódovania v Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Znakovna kodiranja: vsa 8-bitna kodiranja, ki jih zagotavlja Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Знаковна кодирања: сва осмобитна кодирања подржана КуТ‑ом, и ЕБЦДИЦ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Znakovna kodiranja: sva osmobitna kodiranja podržana Qt‑om, i EBCDIC.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Знаковна кодирања: сва осмобитна кодирања подржана КуТ‑ом, и ЕБЦДИЦ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Znakovna kodiranja: sva osmobitna kodiranja podržana Qt‑om, i EBCDIC.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Teckenkodningar: Alla 8-bitars kodningar som tillhandahålls av Qt, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Karakter kodlamaları: Qt tarafından verilen tüm 8-bit kodlamaları, EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Кодування символів: підтримка усіх 8-бітових кодувань, які підтримуються у Qt, EBCDIC.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCharacter encodings: All 8-bit encodings as supplied by Qt, EBCDICxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">字符编码：Qt 提供的全部 8 位编码，EBCDIC</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">字元編碼：所有 Qt 與 EBCDIC 5 支援的八位元編碼方式</li>
      <li>Fast data rendering on screen</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Renderització ràpida de les dades a la pantalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Renderització ràpida de les dades a la pantalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Schnelles Rendern der Daten auf dem Bildschirm</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Γρήγορη αποτύπωση χαρακτήρων στην οθόνη</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Fast data rendering on screen</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Visualización rápida de datos en la pantalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Andmete kiire renderdamine ekraanil</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Pantailan datuen errendatze azkarra</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Datan nopea näyttäminen</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Rendu rapide des données à l'écran</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Os datos móstranse rapidamente na pantalla.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Gyors adatrenderelés a kijelzőn</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Rendition rapide de datos sur schermo</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Perenderan data yang cepat pada layar</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Resa veloce dei dati sullo schermo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">화면에서의 빠른 데이터 렌더링</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Snelle weergave van gegevens op het scherm</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Rask datavising på skjermen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Szybkie wyświetlane danych na ekranie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Apresentação rápida dos dados no ecrã</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Apresentação rápida dos dados na tela</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Быстрый показ данных на экране</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Rýchle zobrazovanie údajov na obrazovke</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Hitro izrisovanje podatkov na zaslonu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Брзо рендеровање података на екрану.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Brzo renderovanje podataka na ekranu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Брзо рендеровање података на екрану.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Brzo renderovanje podataka na ekranu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Snabb dataåtergivning på skärmen</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Ekranda hızlı veri gerçekleme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Швидкий показ даних на екрані.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFast data rendering on screenxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在屏幕上快速渲染数据</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">快速螢幕資料繪制</li>
      <li>Multiple open files</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Múltiples fitxers oberts</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Múltiples fitxers oberts</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Otevření více souborů</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Mehrere geöffnete Dateien</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Άνοιγμα πολλαπλών αρχείων</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Multiple open files</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite abrir varios archivos a la vez</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Paljude failide korraga avamise võimalus</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Irekitako fitxategi aniztuna</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Useat avoimet tiedostot</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Ouverture de fichiers multiples</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Poden abrirse varios ficheiros de maneira simultánea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Több fájl megnyitása egyszerre</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Files multiple aperite</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Multi pembukaan file</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Più file aperti</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">열린 파일 여러 개</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Meerdere geopende bestanden</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Fleire opne filer samtidig</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Otwieranie wielu plików</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Diversos ficheiros abertos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Diversos arquivos abertos</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Работа с несколькими файлами в одном окне</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Otváranie viacerých súborov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Več odprtih datotek</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Више отворених фајлова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Više otvorenih fajlova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Више отворених фајлова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Više otvorenih fajlova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flera öppna filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çoklu dosya açılması</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість одночасної роботи з декількома файлами.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxMultiple open filesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">同时打开多个文件</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">可開啟多個檔案</li>
      <li>Undo/redo support</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Podrška za poništavanje/ponavljanje akcija</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Admet desfer/refer</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Admet desfer/refer</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Podpora zpět/vpřed</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Zurücknehmen und Wiederherstellen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη αναίρεσης/επανάληψης</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Undo/redo support</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite deshacer y rehacer acciones</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Tagasivõtmiste ja uuestitegemiste toetus</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Desegin/berregin euskarria</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tuki muutosten kumoamiselle ja tekemiselle uudelleen</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge de « annuler » et « refaire »</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite desfacer e refacer operacións.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Visszavonás/újra műveletek támogatása</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Supporto de annulla/reface</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Dukungan urungkan/lanjurkan</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per annulla/rifai</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">실행 취소 / 다시 실행 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning ongedaan maken/opnieuw</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Støtte for angring/omgjering</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa cofnij/ponów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para desfazer/refazer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para desfazer/refazer</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Отмена и возврат действий</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora Späť/Znova</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora razveljavitvam/uveljavitvam</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Опозивање и понављање.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Opozivanje i ponavljanje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Опозивање и понављање.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Opozivanje i ponavljanje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för ångra och gör om</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Geri al/yeniden yap desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка скасовування та повторення дій.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxUndo/redo supportxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持撤销/重做</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">復原/重做支援</li>
      <li>Structures tool for analyzing and editing based on user-creatable structure definitions</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Eina d'estructures per a analitzar i editar, basada en definicions de l'estructura que pot crear l'usuari</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Eina d'estructures per a analitzar i editar, basada en definicions de l'estructura que pot crear l'usuari</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Strukturen-Werkzeug für die Untersuchung und Bearbeitung auf der Basis von benutzerdefinierten Strukturdefinitionen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εργαλείο δομών για ανάλυση και επεξεργασία με βάση ορισμούς δομών που δημιουργεί ο χρήστης</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Structures tool for analysing and editing based on user-creatable structure definitions</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Herramientas de estructuras para analizar y editar basándose en definiciones de estructuras creadas por el usuario</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Struktuuride tööriist analüüsimiseks ja muutmiseks vastavalt kasutaja loodud struktuuridefinitsioonidele</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Aztertzeko eta editatzeko egituren tresna, erabiltzaileak sor ditzakeen egitura definizioetan oinarritua</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Rakennetyökalu datan analysointiin ja muokkaamiseen; perustuu rakennemääritelmiin, joita käyttäjät voivat luoda</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Outil de structures pour l'analyse et l'édition basé des définitions de structures créées par l'utilisateur</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Ferramenta de estruturas para analizar e editar baseándose en definicións de estruturas creadas polo usuario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Struktúra eszközök a felhasználó által létrehozott struktúradefiníciók elemzésére és szerkesztésére</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Instrumento de structuras per analysar e modificar basate sur definitiones de structure creabile de usator (user-creatable structure)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Alat struktur untuk menganalisis dan mengedit berdasarkan pada struktur pengguna yang dapat diciptakan</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Strumento per le strutture per analizzare e modificare in base a definizioni di strutture dell'utente</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">사용자가 만들 수 있는 구조 정의를 기반으로 분석 및 편집하는 구조 도구</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Het hulpmiddel Structuren voor analyseren en bewerking op door de gebruiker gemaakte structuurdefinities</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Strukturverktøy for analyse og redigering basert på strukturar som du sjølv kan definera</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie struktur do analizowania i edytowania na podstawie definicji struktur tworzonych przez użytkownika</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ferramenta de estruturas para analisar e editar com base em definições de estruturas criadas pelo utilizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramenta de estruturas para análise e edição com base em definições de estruturas criadas pelo usuário</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Инструмент для работы со структурами данных, вы можете сами создавать определения для новых структур данных</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nástroj štruktúr na analýzu a úpravu založený na používateľom vytvoriteľných definíciách štruktúr</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Orodje struktur za preučevanje in urejanje, ki temelji na uporabniško ustvarjenih določilih struktur</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Алатка структура за анализирање и уређивање на основу кориснички задатих дефиниција структура.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Alatka struktura za analiziranje i uređivanje na osnovu korisnički zadatih definicija struktura.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Алатка структура за анализирање и уређивање на основу кориснички задатих дефиниција структура.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Alatka struktura za analiziranje i uređivanje na osnovu korisnički zadatih definicija struktura.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Strukturverktyg för att undersökning och redigering baserat på användarskapade strukturdefinitioner</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kullanıcının oluşturabildiği yapı tanımlamalarına dayalı analiz ve düzenleme yapmak için araçlar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">За допомогою інструменту «Структури» можна аналізувати та редагувати масиви байтів на основі створених користувачем визначень структур.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxStructures tool for analyzing and editing based on user-creatable structure definitionsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">用于分析和编辑用户自建结构体定义的结构体工具</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">基於使用者建立的結構定義做分析與編輯的工具</li>
      <li>And more...</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">i još %1</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">I més...</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">I més...</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">A další...</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Und noch mehr ...</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Και πολλά άλλα...</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">And more...</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Y más...</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ja veel palju muud...</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Eta gehiago...</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Ja muuta…</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Et plus…</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">E máis…</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">És még sok minden más…</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">E altere ...</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Dan selebihnya...</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">E altro ancora...</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">그리고 더...</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">En meer...</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Og mykje meir …</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">I więcej...</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">E mais...</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">E mais...</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Și altele...</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">И многое другое...</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">A viac...</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">In še več …</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">И више...</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">I više...</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">И више...</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">I više...</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Med mera ...</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Ve daha fazlası...</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Та багато чого іншого…</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAnd more...xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">以及更多...</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">還有更多...</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/Okteta/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=okteta</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=okteta</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=okteta</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/okteta.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <provides>
    <binary>okteta</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.okteta.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.26.6" date="2021-03-29"/>
    <release version="0.26.5" date="2021-02-01"/>
    <release version="0.26.4" date="2020-07-28"/>
    <release version="0.26.3" date="2020-02-02"/>
  </releases>
  <update_contact>kossebau_at_kde.org</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
